(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.2",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
あ、緊張してきたな...
Ah, I'm getting nervous...
や、でもなんか、帰りたい。帰っていいですか？
No, but somehow, I want to go home. Can I go home?
まじ緊張する、あー...
I'm really nervous, ah...
あ、でも、楽しみではある、ね？
Ah, but I'm looking forward to it, right?
みんな楽しみにしてくれてるのかな...
I wonder if everyone is looking forward to it...
へへ、う、でも、でもこれキツいんだろうな...
Hehe, ugh, but, but this is gonna be tough...
ちょっと、みんな会えるの楽しみなんだ。早く早くー。
Hey, I'm looking forward to meeting everyone. Hurry, hurry~.
まだかな、まだかな、まだかな...
Is it time yet, is it time yet, is it time yet...
よし、準備して...
Alright, let's get ready...
みんなー！どーもー！
Everyone! Hello~!
うわ、失礼します！すいません！ちょっと失礼しますね！
Whoa, excuse me! Sorry! Just passing through!
どーも、沙花叉です！
Hello, it's Sakamata!
ども、ども、ども！
Hi, hi, hi!
や、これ何の再現かわかる？
Hey, do you know what this is a recreation of?
わかる人、わかるかな？
Do those who know, get it?
ではでは、ちょっと降り…降りたいんですけど
Well then, I want to... step down
あの、降りる時ちょっと恥ずかしいから
Um, it's a bit embarrassing when I step down
あっち見ててて、あっち見ててて、あっち見て！
So look over there, look over there, look over there!
やだ！見ないで！
No! Don't look!
はい！お、みんな、どうどう？ステージが見えてるね。
Yes! Oh, everyone, how is it? You can see the stage now.
うー、じゃあ
Ngh- well then
バクバクバクーンだわ！
Baku-baku-bakuun!
秘密結社holoXの掃除屋、インターン…インターン生の沙花叉クロヱです！
I'm the cleaner of secret society holoX, the intern... intern Sakamata Chloe!
どうもー！いただきまーす！
Hello! Let's eat!
え、みんなちょっと心配したでしょう、今回は。
Um, you all were probably a bit worried this time.
あれ？ちょっと音声入っちゃったんじゃないの？どうしようどうしようと思ったと思うんですけど
Thinking, "Wait, did some audio leak? What should we do?", I bet.
今回は事故ではないです。
This time it's not an accident.
ちゃんとね、音声さんも付いてくれてる演出でした！いえーい！
It was a planned performance with the audio staff! Yay!
いや、よかったよかった。
Phew, I'm glad, I'm glad.
本当にね、ちょっと事故だと思われたら怖いなと思ったので。よかったよかった。
Really, I was afraid it would be mistaken for an accident. I'm glad, I'm glad.
うわ！何これ？
Whoa! What's this?
何？これ。え？
What? This. Eh?
チップ？これチップじゃない？
A chip? Isn't this a chip?
チップだよね？え？
It's a chip, right? Eh?
やったー！何か分かんないけどやったー！いえーい！
Yay! I don't know what it is, but yay! Yay!
チップもらった。
I got a chip.
あ、遅刻しなかったから、起きれたかららしいです。え？何か弄られてない？
Ah, apparently it's because I wasn't late, because I woke up on time. Eh? Am I being teased?
え、でも見て、可愛い！え、ちょっと分かんないけど嬉しい、やったー！
Eh, but look, it's cute! Eh, I don't quite get it, but I'm happy, yay!
じゃあちょっと仕まっとこうかな、沙花叉。
I guess I'll put it away, Sakamata.
あ、チップ仕まうと言えばもうここですよねって感じで、失礼します。
Ah, if you're putting away a chip, it's gotta be here, right? Excuse me.
よいしょー！オッケーです。
Heave-ho! Okay.
ね、どうどう？3Dの沙花叉。
Hey, how is it? 3D Sakamata.
ね、可愛い可愛い？どうどう？見て、可愛いでしょ。
Hey, isn't she cute? How is it? Look, she's cute, right?
うわ！エッチなアングル！
Whoa! Lewd angle!
きゃー！見ないで！
Eek! Don't look!
うんだ。ああ、よかったよかった。
Right. Ah, I'm glad, I'm glad.
なんとね、沙花叉クロヱちゃんももちろん可愛いんですが
Not only is Sakamata Chloe-chan cute, of course, but...
このステージ見てほしいんだよね！
I want you to see this stage!
見てー！うわぁー！これすごいでしょ。
Look! Whoa! This is amazing, right?
水族館ステージになってます！いえーい！
It's an aquarium stage! Yay!
何かね、リボンとかが沙花叉のこのリボンとおそろいになったり
Somehow, the ribbons and stuff match this ribbon of Sakamata's
あとこのシャチの噴水。
And then there's this orca fountain.
ちょっとあの、シャチってこんな水吐いたっけみたいな感じでもあるんですけど
It's a bit like, did orcas always spray water like this?
よく見たら怖いんですけど、シャチの噴水があったりとか。
If you look closely it's a bit scary, but there's an orca fountain and all.
そしてね、なんと飼育員さんたちが3Dになっているとかどうとか。
And then, what's more, the keepers have become 3D or something.
うわぁー！飼育員怖！
Whoa! The keeper is scary!
絵面めっちゃ怖いけどな。
The visuals are super scary though.
これね、飼育員さんたち沙花叉の仮面つけた仕様になってます。
These keepers are in a version wearing Sakamata's mask.
どうどう？飼育員さんたちも3D化しました。
How is it? The keepers have also been 3D-ified.
え、あ、みんなたくさんの人が見に来てくれてるみたい。
Eh, ah, it looks like many people have come to watch.
ありがとうございます！いえーい！
Thank you so much! Yay!
え、あのー十万人見に来てくれてるらしいです。ぎっしり…
Eh, I heard 100,000 people are watching. It's packed...
ありがとうございます！みんなありがとう！
Thank you so much! Thank you everyone!
ではではでは、実はまだ沙花叉のステージにはたくさんの沙花叉要素が隠されているので
Well then, well then, actually there are still many Sakamata elements hidden on the stage
探してみてこの後。まだまだたくさんありよ。
So try looking for them after this. There are still many more.
ではでは、そろそろ気になってるんじゃないですか？
Well then, aren't you getting curious by now?
沙花叉ちゃんのこの仮面…外してほしい？
About Sakamata-chan's mask... do you want me to take it off?
ねーねー、外してほしい？
Hey, hey, do you want me to take it off?
ねーねーねーねーねー、外してほしい？
Hey hey hey hey hey, do you want me to take it off?
えーどうしようかな。どうしようかな。
Hmm, what should I do. What should I do.
え、外してみてもいいけど、んー、んー…
Well, I could try taking it off, but, hmm, hmm...
あ！そうだそうだ！
Ah! That's right!
あの飼育員さんたち、何か<><お魚、沙花叉の待機の時のあれをくれたら
Those keepers, if they give me the <>< fish from my waiting screen...
沙花叉にご褒美があるらしい！
...I heard there's a reward for Sakamata!
なので、ちょっとみんな…
So, everyone...
小なり大なり、小なりお魚、流してください！
Big or small, please send some fish my way!
そのご褒美貰っとるも…ちょっとやってあげようかなーっと思ったり、
I'm receiving rewards for it... so I thought I might do something for you,
仮面外してあげようかなーっと思ってるんですけども、
I was thinking about maybe taking off my mask...
流して流して！どうぞ！
Send them, send them! Go ahead!
ねえ、違うでしょ？それじゃないでしょ？ねえ、みんなちゃんと見てんだよおさか…
Hey, that's not right, is it? It's not that, right? Hey, everyone is watching the fi—
うわあああああ！やだあああああ！
Whoaaa! Noooo!
なんか来たんだけど！うわあああああ！
Something just came! Whoaaa!
何これ？！やば！えっ…
What is this?! This is crazy! Uh...
お魚？
A fish?
お魚来たよね…リアルすぎん？ちょっとリアルすぎん？
A fish really came... Isn't it too realistic? Isn't it a bit too real?
えっ、えっ、みんなが、ねえ、みんながコメントするから！
Eh, eh, because everyone... hey, because everyone is commenting!
うわあああああ！何これ！ねえ、多いよ！うわあああああ！きもい！
Whoaaa! What is this! Hey, there are too many! Whoaaa! Gross!
おい、沙花叉の3Dお披露目でしょーが！何これ！
Hey, this is Sakamata's 3D debut! What's with this?!
持てるのこれ？
Can I hold this?
うわ、持てる！うわ持てるよこれ！どっこいしょ！よいしょ！
Whoa, I can! I can actually hold it! Heave-ho! Up we go!
みんな、みんなお魚さんだよ。ほらお披露目。
Everyone, look, it's Mr. Fish. Here's the debut.
これが見たかったんでしょ？んちゅっちゅ、んむじゅんじゅんじゅん…
This is what you wanted to see, right? *kissing sounds*
ねえ何これ、きしょい！気持ち悪いし！
Hey, what is this, gross! And it's creepy!
うわああ！活きが良すぎて！うわああ！
Whoaaa! It's too lively! Whoaaa!
おらあ！何これきもい！
Take that! What is this, so gross!
でもね、みんな。どう？どっちが可愛いの？
But hey, everyone. What do you think? Which one is cuter?
どう？沙花叉とこのお魚、どっちが可愛い？ねえねえ。
How about it? Between Sakamata and this fish, which is cuter? Hey, hey.
もちろん、もちろん沙花叉だよね？そうだよね？あー良かった良かった。
Of course, it's Sakamata, right? Right? Oh, thank goodness.
じゃ、ねえねえねえ、さーちゃんもういいよ、いいよもうコメント！おいおい！大量にいるから！
Now then, hey, that's enough comments! Hey! There's a massive amount of them!
ねえ、処理落ちとかしたらどうすんの？怖いでしょーがこれ！
Hey, what if the stream starts lagging? This is scary!
やめてって言ってんの！おらおらおらおら！おらおらおらおら！
I said stop it! Ora ora ora ora!
よしよし。はぁ、まあでも、これじゃ仮面は外してあげられないなー。
There, there. *sigh* Well, with things like this, I can't take off my mask.
みんな残念でしたー。悔しいでしょー？
Too bad for all of you. Frustrating, isn't it?
残念残念。じゃ、このままいっちゃおっかなー。
Too bad, too bad. Well, I guess I'll just keep going like this.
この動画を見てください
Please watch this video
この動画を見てください…何これ？
"Please watch this video"... What is this?
サプライズ？
A surprise?
いやー、そうだよねみんな、お祝いしたいよね、沙花叉クロヱの3D配信だもんね。
Well, of course, everyone wants to celebrate Sakamata Chloe's 3D debut stream.
えー何だろう何だろう、見てみよ見てみよ。
I wonder what it is. Let's see, let's see.
何？
What?
これ見たことあるよ。やだ、見たくない！
I've seen this before. No, I don't want to look!
やだやだ、何これ何これ！
No, no! What is this, what is this!
うわああ、目離したいのに！うわああ何これ！
Whoaaa, I want to look away! Whoaaa, what is this!
助けて！スタッフさん助けて！うわあああああ！
Help me! Staff, help! Whoaaa!
仮面をはずしてください
Please take off the mask
仮面を外してください？いやいや、沙花叉クロヱが仮面を外すわけないじゃん。
"Please take off the mask"? No way, there's no way Sakamata Chloe would take off her mask.
絶対外してあげないからね！いや、沙花叉はそんな、たかが千の…うっ。
I'm definitely not taking it off! Sakamata is not someone who— Ugh.
あ、仮面を脱いでしまった…うわあああ！
Ah, I took off the mask... Whoaaa!
はい。というわけで、えー、沙花叉の3Dこんな感じとなってます。どう？可愛いでしょー、なあなあ？
Okay! So, Sakamata's 3D looks like this. Well? Cute, isn't it? Right?
どう？あっちこっち。ふふふ。
How is it? From every angle. Hehe.
可愛いでしょー！
I'm cute, right!
じゃあ早速ね、この水族館で、遊んでいきたいと思いまーす！
So now, let's have some fun here in this aquarium!
ポロンビア！ふふふ。
Polonbia! Hehe.
じゃあ、まずは何してほしい沙花叉に？ねえみんな、何してほしいの？
First of all, what do you want Sakamata to do? Hey everyone, what do you want?
ちょっとみんなのコメント見て、拾ってっちゃおっかなー。何してほしい、何してほしい？何だい何だい？
I'll take a look at the comments and pick some out. What do you want me to do? What's it gonna be?
みんな可愛いしか言ってないじゃん！ねえ何してほしいか言ってよ、言って！言って！
Everyone is just saying "cute"! Tell me what you want me to do! Tell me! Say it!
ジャンプ？えっ、ジャンプ、いいよ！ほい！
Jump? Oh, jump? Sure! There!
ジャンプ、ジャンプ、ジャンプ、ジャンプ！どう？
Jump, jump, jump, jump! How's that?
沙花叉が一番エッチだと思う飛び方しようか。これぐらい。
Should I do the jump that I think is the sexiest? About like this.
これ、これ、これぐらいが一番エッチだと思いませんか？
Don't you think this... this... about this is the sexiest?
ジャンプよりこっちの方がよくない？ふふふ。
Isn't this better than jumping? Hehe.
怒られるまた。嫌だよー、大人たちの冷たい目が来る。
I'm gonna get scolded again. I hate it, the cold stares from the adults.
はい！まあとりあえずはこの、3Dの素晴らしいボディを手に入れたからにはね、沙花叉のフィジカルのお手並み拝見ってやつをね、
Okay! Well, now that I've gotten this wonderful 3D body, let's see what I can do physically!
皆さんに、見せてあげようかな、と
I guess I'll show it to everyone.
甘えます！
I'm going to be spoiled!
じゃ、いきますか。
Well, shall we go?
せーの、ドン！
Ready, go!
沙花叉スポーツ
Sakamata Sports
沙花叉スポーツ、イエーイ！
Sakamata Sports, yay!
（スシ、トーン、パッ）
(Sushi, tone, pa!)
はい、沙花叉スポーツです。
Yes, this is Sakamata Sports.
まあね、沙花叉クロヱ、最近、配信で鍛えた腹筋もありますし、
Well, Sakamata Chloe has abs trained from recent streams,
余裕なんじゃないかな、なんて思っちゃってるんですけども。
so I'm thinking this might be a breeze.
はい！じゃ、まずはね、
Okay! First of all,
定番の、反復横跳び、
the standard side-to-side jumps,
あ、反復横跳び、反復横跳び。
Ah, side-to-side jumps, side-to-side jumps.
はい、スポーツテスト的なことだよね、多分。
Yeah, it's like a fitness test, probably.
スポーツテスト、やりたいと思います！
I'm going to do a fitness test!
甘えます！何かシュシュッ、みたいな動きでしょ？
I'm being spoiled! It's like a 'swish-swish' movement, right?
いや、できる沙花叉。だってもうダンスレッスンもしたし、
No, Sakamata can do it. I've even had dance lessons,
うん、絶対できるから。任せてください。
so I can definitely do it. Just leave it to me.
いきますか！
Here we go!
何秒？何秒あるの？
How many seconds? How many seconds do I have?
20秒。20秒ね。
20 seconds. 20 seconds, okay.
余裕だよ。お、準備はや。
It's easy. Oh, setup is fast.
準備はやいな。
That setup was fast.
いきますよ。
I'm starting.
はい！
Go!
11！
11!
お。
Oh.
終わった。
It's over.
11回。
11 times.
イエーイ！
Yay!
やば。沙花叉の、沙花叉のね、え、なんか、
Whoa. Sakamata's... wait, what?
あれ？神の声が、動き方が変だとか、
Huh? The 'Voice of God' says my movement is weird,
線10本ぐらいないとか、失礼じゃん！どう考えても！
or that I missed about 10 lines. That's rude! No matter how you look at it!
ちゃんと頑張ってたでしょうが！
I was working hard, you know!
え、でもさ、反復横跳びってこんなんだよね？
But wait, side-to-side jumps are like this, right?
え、違う？俺の知ってる反復横跳びと違った？
Was it different from the side-to-side jumps I know?
え、数え方も間違ってた？え、なんで！
Wait, was my counting wrong too? Why!
嘘だ！絶対嘘！え、本当に違うんですか？
No way! Definitely lying! Is it really different?
あ、すみませんでした。あの、でも、でも、
Ah, I'm sorry. But, but...
あの、概ねOK、跳べてましたから、
it was mostly OK, I was jumping,
やったやった。
yay yay.
あ、え、トレンド1位なんだった、今。
Oh, wait, it says I'm trending #1 now.
みんなありがとう！もっともっと、
Thank you everyone! Please keep on
「#沙花叉クロヱ3D」で呟いてくれると嬉しいなって思います。
tweeting with #SakamataChloe3D, I'd be so happy.
よろしくお願いします。
Please keep up the support.
はあ、までもしゃーないと思うんだけど、
Sigh, well, I guess it can't be helped,
まあ、これコート着てるからな。
but, I'm wearing this coat.
これ300キロあるしな。重いよな。いや、しかも暑。
This weighs 300kg. It's heavy. And it's hot.
やっぱもう運動したからアッチアチだ。
As expected, I'm burning up from the exercise.
もうこれはしょうがないな。アッチアチだからかな。
It can't be helped. It's because I'm burning up.
あー、本当じゃないって。
Ah, that's not true.
この動画を見てください
Please watch this video.
いや、もう騙されないよ、沙花叉クロヱは。
No, Sakamata Chloe won't be fooled anymore.
その動画を見たら、絶対に、
If I watch that video, definitely,
何か悪い大人たちが何かを考えているってことでしょ。
it means some bad adults are plotting something, right?
その動画なんて絶対沙花叉クロヱは見ないからね。
Sakamata Chloe is definitely not watching that video.
わかった？早いよ、準備が、準備が早いよ！
Got it? That setup is way too fast!
ね、よくない準備、絶対違うよね。
Wait, that's a bad setup, it's definitely different.
ねえ、もういいって。見たよね。ねえ、ダメだ。
Hey, enough already. You saw it. Hey, no way.
ああ、もう大好きだって。助けて、おかしなことになってる。
Ah, I love you guys. Help, something weird is happening.
もう今回は、特に、もう何も、
This time, especially, there should be nothing...
できないはずなんだけどな。
nothing that can be done.
コートを脱いでください
Please take off your coat.
え？コートを脱いでください。
Huh? 'Please take off your coat'.
いやいや、暑いとは言ったけど、コートは脱がないですから。
No, no, I said it's hot, but I'm not taking off my coat.
脱ぎそうで脱がない女っていうのが沙花叉クロヱですから、
Being a woman who looks like she'll strip but won't, that's Sakamata Chloe,
絶対に脱いだりしませんから。
so I'm definitely not taking it off.
わかりました？聞いてる？みんな聞いてる？
Got it? Are you listening? Is everyone listening?
うわー！脱いじゃったー！
Whoa! It came off!
2回目なんよ。伝統なんよ。
It's the second time. It's a tradition.
はい。ということで、ありがとうございます。
Yes. So, thank you very much.
え、でもこれいいのかな？
Wait, is this really okay?
え、いいんだよね。一応OK。
Well, it's fine, right? For now, it's OK.
事後だし。さっきの。
After what just happened.
え、これ大丈夫？本当に？
Is this okay? Really?
え、でもいいんだよね。いいって言われたから。
But it's fine, right? Because I was told it's fine.
え、可愛いでしょ。どう？
It's cute, isn't it? How is it?
いい感じ？
Does it look good?
やっぱコートなしもエッチだな、みたいな。うわー！
I guess without a coat it's sexy, or something. Whoa!
あんまり見てちゃダメ。ダメ。
Don't look too much. No.
はい。というわけで、次の種目。
All right. So, the next event.
ドドン！
Ta-da!
沙花叉ショー
Sakamata Show
状態そらし！
Back extension!
状態そらし
Back extension
はい。
Yes.
状態そらし。
Back extension.
沙花叉クロヱ、上体反らし...
Sakamata Chloe, back extension...
やったこと、まあ、あるっちゃあるけど、うん。
I've done it, well, I guess I have, but, yeah.
何センチぐらいが基本なんですかね？
How many centimeters is the standard?
何センチぐらい... あ、メジャー、メジャー。
How many centimeters... Ah, tape measure, tape measure.
あ、でもでもでも、
Ah, but but but,
たぶんなんだけど...
I think...
60とか65とか68とか、60ぐらい行けんじゃだい？
Maybe 60, 65, 68... I can probably do about 60?
60とか無理かな？
Is 60 impossible?
L、いけそうじゃない？ 頑張れば。
Size L, doesn't it seem possible? If I try hard.
ちょっとやってみる？
Want to try it?
やってみるか、実際。行きますか。
Shall I try, actually. Let's go.
沙花叉クロヱちゃんの上体反らし。
Sakamata Chloe's back extension.
あー、あの企画とはいえかわいそうだよね、床に袖るの。そう思わないみんな？
Ah... even if it's a project, it's a bit sad to be on the floor. Don't you all think so?
いくよ！
Here I go!
みんないい？ いくよ？
Everyone ready? Here I go?
沙花叉の好きなタイミングで、いくよ？
At my own timing, here I go?
せーの、はい！
One, two, go!
はい！ どう？ どう？ 何センチですか？
Yes! How is it? How is it? How many centimeters?
何センチ？ 何センチ？ どう？ どう？
How many? How many? How is it? How is it?
え、何みんなすま... ねー、ねー、ねー、ねー、何センチ何センチ？
Eh, why is everyone... Hey, hey, hey, how many centimeters?
おい！ 俺を放っとくんじゃね！
Hey! Don't leave me hanging!
ねー何センチ何センチだって聞いて、早く！
Hey, how many centimeters, I asked, hurry!
ねー何センチ！ 何センチ！
Hey, how many centimeters! How many!
あー無理、全部無理。
Ah, impossible, everything is impossible.
え、何？ 沙花叉死んだ？ え？
Eh, what? Did Sakamata die? Eh?
何センチでした。え、15センチ。
The result... was 15 cm.
ねーー！ 絶対そんなことない！
No way! There's no way!
いや、絶対そんなことなくない？
No, isn't there no way?
え、今もっと上がってたよね？ え？
Eh, I was up higher just now, right? Eh?
絶対理不尽。え？
Totally unfair. Eh?
僕操作されてるんだけど。
I'm being manipulated.
え、もう一回？ え？ 台本にないじゃん。
Eh, one more time? Eh? It's not in the script.
え？ マジで？ あー、いいよじゃあ。
Eh? Seriously? Ah, fine then.
しょうがないなあ。もう一回。いくよ。
Can't be helped. One more time. Here I go.
ちょっとこのさー、メジャーもちゃんとして。
Make sure the tape measure is set properly too.
いくよ。せーの、はい！
Here I go. One, two, go!
どう？ どう？ めっちゃ上がってる、めっちゃ上がってる。
How is it? How is it? It's way up, way up.
ねーどうですか？ ねー何センチは今で、今。
Hey, how is it? Hey, how many centimeters right now, right now.
お前今測ってとか言って。何セ...
You, tell them to measure now. How many...
全部無理。
Everything's impossible.
何センチなわけないだろ。何センチなわけないだろ。
There's no way it's that many centimeters. No way it's that many.
絶対変。絶対変。次行きましょうかじゃないでしょ。
It's definitely weird. Definitely weird. It shouldn't be "shall we move on".
ね、次行きましょうかじゃないでしょ。
Hey, it shouldn't be "shall we move on".
ひどい... 頑張ったのに。
Cruel... even though I worked so hard.
はい、ということで。
Okay, so.
最後さ、そう、沙花叉クロヱの自信がある、おまちかね、腹筋です！
Lastly, yes, the one Sakamata Chloe is confident in, the long-awaited abdominal exercises!
いや、もうこれはね、普段からやってますので。
Well, this is something I do regularly.
じゃあ、行きますか。
So, shall we go.
何これ何これ？ え？
What is this, what is this? Eh?
なんか、腹筋ローラーじゃないこれ？
Isn't this an ab roller?
腹筋ローラーですよねこれね？
It's an ab roller, isn't it?
え？ いや、腹筋でしょやるの。は？
Eh? No, I'm doing sit-ups. Huh?
え、腹筋ローラーやるんですか？ 地獄じゃない？
Eh, am I doing the ab roller? Isn't that hell?
え、地獄じゃない？
Eh, isn't that hell?
え、沙花叉これじゃなくないやるの？ かわいそうくない？ え？
Eh, isn't this not what I'm supposed to do? Isn't it pitiful? Eh?
あー！ お願いします！ 許すですじゃない！
Ah! Please! It's not "I forgive you"!
ねーやばいやばいやばい！ 死ぬ死ぬ死ぬ！
Hey, this is bad, bad, bad! I'm gonna die, die, die!
死ぬ！ あーーーー！
Die! Aaaa!
これが望みか！ なあ！
Is this what you wanted! Well!
これでいいのか大人たちは！
Is this okay with you adults!
良くないよねモレちゃん。モレちゃんグッドサイン出してるんだけど。
It's not good, right, Mare-chan. Mare-chan is giving a thumbs up though.
ねーこっち来る？
Hey, you coming here?
ねーもうやら... もうやだ。
Hey, I won't... I don't want to anymore.
かわいそう沙花叉。
Poor Sakamata.
え？ なんか普通の腹筋だったら自信あるんですかって聞かれたんですけど。はい！
Eh? I was asked if I'm confident if it's just normal sit-ups. Yes!
超自信あります。
I'm super confident.
今やってるから。
Because I'm doing them now.
え？ 30秒で何回いける？
Eh? How many can I do in 30 seconds?
え、そりゃもう40ぐらい行くんじゃない？
Eh, probably about 40?
いや、40ぐらい行っちゃうし。いいですよ。
No, I'll definitely do about 40. Fine.
あー、やっていって。じゃあ40ぐらい行きますか。
Ah, I'll do it. Then, shall we aim for 40?
ちょっとやりましょう。えっとどうする？
Let's do it. Well, what do I do?
おい。こう？ こうで、こう。
Hey. Like this? Like this, then this.
え？ 違う？
Eh? Am I wrong?
え？ 違うの？ あれ？ 大人たちが困ってる。
Eh? It's wrong? Huh? The adults are confused.
あー、こっち？ あー、こっちか。あー、わかった。
Ah, this way? Ah, it's this way. Ah, I get it.
はい。いくよ。あー、足...
Okay. Here I go. Ah, my legs...
あ、ちょ、あ、い、いってぇ！　笑　いい？　いい？
Ah, wait, ah, o-ouch! (laughs) Ready? Ready?
いち！
One!
に！
Two!
なんか、腹筋のある生活ちょっと辛いんだけど。
Living a life with sit-ups is a bit tough.
よん！
Four!
ご！
Five!
ろく！
Six!
なな！
Seven!
はち！
Eight!
きゅう！
Nine!
じゅう！
Ten!
どう？　な、え、10回！
How's that? Wh- eh, 10 times!
え、これどういうことですかって怒られてるんだけど。
Eh, I'm being scolded, "What's the meaning of this?"
そらさ、だってさ腹筋のあるって聞いてなかったよね坂又ね。
Well, because I hadn't heard about having sit-ups, right Sakamata?
坂本、マネちゃんも考えてんだけど、ねぇ！
Sakamoto, Mane-chan is also thinking about it, hey!
ぎゃー！　待って！　ぎゃー！
Gyaa! Wait! Gyaa!
危ない危ない危ない！　やだ、待って！
Dangerous, dangerous, dangerous! No, wait!
ねぇ疲れてるよね、今どう考えても追い打ちだよねこんな。
Hey, I'm tired, right? This is clearly a follow-up attack.
ねぇキモいんだってそんでビジュがヤバいって。どう考えてもリアルだろ。
Hey, it's gross and the visuals are crazy. It looks way too real.
こんなにね、疲れちゃったんですけど。
I've gotten this tired, but...
ま、じゃあ次に移りたいと思います。ひどいよね。
Well, then, I'd like to move on. It's cruel, isn't it?
はい、次は、ドン！　沙花叉ショー！　イェーイ！
Okay, next up is... Bam! Sakamata Show! Yay!
沙花叉ショー
Sakamata Show
まぁね水族館だから坂又のシャチのショーを見せてあげたいと思います。
Since we're at an aquarium, I'd like to show you Sakamata's orca show.
そしてこちらを使います。
And I'll be using this.
ぽっ！　わあ！　スイカ！
Pop! Wow! A watermelon!
5万？　腕力ヤバすぎねぇ。
50,000? My grip strength is way too crazy.
こちらのスイカを使って、えー、ヘディングをしたいと思います。
I'll use this watermelon to do some headers.
連続で7回、
If I can do it 7 times in a row,
7回、7回できれば坂又の勝ち目。
7 times, if I do it 7 times, Sakamata wins.
いくよ！
Here I go!
いきます！　マネちゃんが持ってんだよ今。
Here I go! Mane-chan is holding it now.
マネちゃんがフェイントしようとしてる、ねぇ！　早く！
Mane-chan is trying to feint, hey! Hurry up!
はい！　1！
Yes! One!
はい！　2！
Yes! Two!
おい、よしに。
Hey, watch it.
はい！　3！　ぎゃー！
Yes! Three! Gyaa!
よし、3。おっけおっけ。
Okay, 3. Good, good.
4！
Four!
でなんかさぁ、持ってる挙動と投げる場所違うんだけど。
Also, the way you're holding it and where you're throwing it are different.
5！
Five!
6！
Six!
7！
Seven!
ねぇ、ひどくない？　え？
Hey, isn't that cruel? Eh?
なんかさぁ、投げ方が完全に落とす気満々...
The way you're throwing it, you're totally trying to make me drop it...
ぎゃー！　待って！　待って！
Gyaa! Wait! Wait!
ねぇ！　ねぇ！
Hey! Hey!
ねぇ、あ、え、クリア？
Hey, ah, eh, clear?
あ、よかった。あ、安心した。
Ah, thank goodness. I'm relieved.
おっ、チップだ！
Oh, it's a chip!
やったー！
Yay!
チップもらった見て見て。
I got a chip, look look.
よかった。ちゃんと勝った。
Good. I actually won.
勝った甲斐があったね。
It was worth winning.
やったー！
Yay!
チップ嬉しい。ありがとうございます。
I'm happy about the chip. Thank you very much.
パン人だからちょっと嬉しくなっちゃう。
I'm a commoner, so this makes me a bit happy.
しまっとこ。
I'll put it away.
しかもいっぱいあるわ。
Wait, there's a lot of them.
やったー！
Yay!
あー疲れた。
Ah, I'm tired.
もう終わりですか？
Is it over yet?
な、なんですか？　はい。
Wh- what is it? Okay.
じゃあ次の沙花叉ショーは、スイカを頭の上でバランスを取りたいと思います。
Well, for the next Sakamata Show, I want to balance a watermelon on my head.
10秒間。
For 10 seconds.
魚、魚じゃない、スイカ。
Fish... no, not fish, watermelon.
10秒間スイカを頭の上でバランス取りたいと思います。
I'll try to balance a watermelon on my head for 10 seconds.
ぎゃー！　魚違う！　違う！
Gyaa! Fish! No! No!
遊ばないで坂又で。やめて！
Don't play with Sakamata. Stop it!
じゃあいきますよ。え？　始まり？
Okay, here I go. Eh? Starting?
1、2、3、4、5、
1, 2, 3, 4, 5...
おっととと、
Whoops...
6、7、8、9、
6, 7, 8, 9...
10！　よし、行けたかな？
10! Alright, did I do it?
イェーイ！　優勝！
Yay! Victory!
あーよかった。あー、安心した。
Ah, thank goodness. I'm relieved.
無事に沙花叉ショーもできましたね。
I was able to safely finish the Sakamata Show too.
おっ！　ぎゃー！　またチップ！
Oh! Gyaa! More chips!
やったー！　見て見て。
Yay! Look, look.
ガチ食べます。ダブチみたい。あーん。
I'm really gonna eat them. Like a Double Cheeseburger. Ahhh.
んっ、でこれチップやないかーい。
Wait, these are actually chips...
よし、しまいますね。
Okay, I'll put them away.
これ入るんか？
Will these fit?
あ、よかった。入りました。
Ah, good. They went in.
ちょっとね、摩擦で痛かったかなって思うんですけど。
I think it might have hurt a bit from friction, though.
よかった。あー。
Great. Whew.
ということで、最後の...
And with that, the last...
最後のコーナーに...
Moving on to the final corner...
移りたいと思います。
...
最後のコーナーは...
The final corner is...
沙花叉ボーナス！
Sakamata Bonus!
沙花叉ボーナス
Sakamata Bonus
イェーイ！
Yay!
はぁ...このコーナーはなんと...
Phew... in this corner...
沙花叉が可愛いポーズをすればするほど...
The more cute poses Sakamata does...
ご褒美がもらえるそうです！
The more rewards I get!
最高！！
Awesome!!
ということで可愛いポーズ...
So, a cute pose...
可愛いポーズか...難しいな。
A cute pose, huh... that's tough.
なんだろう。
What should I do?
じゃあちょっと行きますね。
Okay, here I go.
行きます！
I'm going!
それ！
There!
セクシーポーズ。
Sexy pose.
アハーン！
A-haan!
どう？可愛かった？
How was it? Was it cute?
どう？
Well?
可愛い？
Cute?
なーなーなー。
Hey, hey, hey.
可愛いでしょ。
I'm cute, right?
何でレスポンス無いの？
Why no response?
可愛いよね、みんな。ねぇ...
I'm cute, right everyone? Hey...
何で魚来るの？
Why are fish coming?!
ねぇどっち？それブーイングなの？
Wait, which is it? Is that a boo?
喜んでるの？どっち？
Or are you happy? Which one?!
ねぇどっちなの？分かんないんだよ、それ。
Hey, which is it? I don't understand that!
あっ、可愛い！
Ah, 'cute'!
あ、可愛いって！
Ah, they're saying 'cute'!
みんなが可愛いって言ってくれるなら...
If everyone's saying I'm cute...
可愛いか、ほな。
Then I guess I'm cute.
ほな可愛いか。
Guess I'm cute then.
え、みんなはさ、どんなポーズ...
So, what kind of pose...
して欲しい？
...do you want me to do?
ねぇ、バレッちゃんが...
Hey, Valet-chan...
すっげーさ、なんか疑問そうな顔で...
...has this super doubtful look...
「ま、可愛い...」みたいな感じで返したんだけど。
...and just said, 'Well, I guess it's cute...'
え、ちょっとみんな、どんなポーズして欲しい？
Wait, everyone, what pose do you want to see?
沙花叉がみんなが言ってくれたポーズしようかなって思うんですけど。
I'm thinking of doing the poses you guys suggest.
どんなポーズして欲しい？沙花叉に。
What kind of pose do you want Sakamata to do?
ちょっとやっちゃおうかな。
Maybe I'll just go for it.
沙花叉クロヱちゃん。
Sakamata Chloe-chan.
いや、でも可愛いから。
Well, I'm cute, so...
何しても可愛いかな。
...anything I do should be cute.
かなー。なー。なー。可愛い。
Right? Hey. Hey. Cute.
I字バランス？何？I字バランスって。
I-balance? What's an I-balance?
こう？イェーイ！
Like this? Yay!
だー！
Dah!
いい感じ？
Good?
え？違うの？違うんだ。
Eh? Is that not it? Oh, it's not.
あんなんかすごい笑われてんだけど、今。
Wait, I'm being laughed at a lot right now.
え？ファイティングポーズ？いいよ。
Eh? Fighting pose? Sure.
エイッ！エイッ！エイッ！
Ei! Ei! Ei!
おらぁ！
Oraa!
あとは？あとは？
What else? What else?
どう？
How's this?
Y字バランス？え、これ？
Y-balance? Wait, this?
え、なんかまた大人笑ってんだけど。
Eh, the adults are laughing again.
え、違うの？
Eh, is it wrong?
え、ちょっと分かんないかも。ごめん。
Eh, I might not get it. Sorry.
え、どういうこと？
Wait, what do you mean?
どういうことですか？ちょっと教えていただけると幸いです。
What do you mean? I'd appreciate it if you could tell me.
え？何何？
Eh? What, what?
お、チップ？え、チップ来た！
Oh, chips? Eh, chips are coming!
え、良いんだ！
Oh, that's okay!
え、なんか面白かったからって言われたんだけど。
Eh, they said it's because it was funny.
失礼じゃね？
Isn't that rude?
可愛いと思ってやったんですけど、こっちは。
I did it because I thought it was cute.
イェーイ！3枚ももらえた！
Yay! I got three!
な、なら良かったか。なら良かった。
Well, I guess that's fine then. That's fine.
え、あとはあとは？
What else, what else?
スクワット？
Squats?
バカ、バカ言うんじゃねー。
Don't call me stupid.
行くよ。
Here I go.
はぁ！
Haa!
ちょっと見ないで、ちょっと見ないで！
Don't look, don't look!
ちょっとまずかったかな。ちょっとあの、スクワットは止めよっか。
Maybe that was a bit bad. Let's, uh, stop with the squats.
ね。
Right?
倒立？いや無理バカ言うんじゃねー。
Handstand? No way, don't be ridiculous.
え、なんかさ、みんなさ、可愛いポーズって言ってんのにさ、
Wait, I keep asking for cute poses,
沙花叉で遊ぼうとしてるよね？違うよね、絶対にね、やること。
But you guys are just trying to play with Sakamata, right? That's definitely not what we should be doing.
今やるべきことじゃないよね？何か可愛いのないの？ねぇ。
That's not what we should be doing now, is it? Isn't there something cute? Hey.
可愛いポーズをプリーズなんだけど。ずっと言ってんだけど、ねぇ。
I'm asking for 'cute poses, please'. I've been saying it for a while now, hey.
顔が可愛いから何やっても可愛いってことかな？
Maybe because my face is cute, anything I do is cute?
ちった、んだったらしょうがないなぁ。ねぇ。
Well, if that's the case, I guess it can't be helped. Right?
ガオーのポーズ？あ、いいよ。
A roar pose? Sure.
ガオー！
Gao!
ガオー！ガオー！ガオー！ガオー！
Gao! Gao! Gao! Gao!
どう？
How's that?
どう、どう、どう？いい感じ？
Well? Well? Is it good?
お！はぁ！めっちゃチップ来た！
Oh! Hah! A ton of chips came!
え、良かったー！
Oh, thank goodness!
え、何で何で？
Eh, why, why?
え、めっちゃ、何枚これ。うわ、すごいいっぱいある、5枚！
Whoa, how many are there? Wow, there are so many, five!
え、ありがとうございます。たくさんのチップ。
Eh, thank you very much for all the chips.
やっぱチップ最強！ありがとう、ありがとう。
Chips are the best! Thank you, thank you.
あとあと？何だい？
What else? What is it?
ちょ、さっきから、ふざけっぱなし。え、ジョジョ立ち？
Wait, you've just been messing around. A JoJo pose?
いいよ、やろうか。
Fine, let's do it.
どうだい？ジョジョ立ち。
How's this? A JoJo pose.
できてる？できてる、これ。
Am I doing it? Am I doing it right?
どう？
Well?
なってる？なってる？難しいんだけど。
Am I? Am I? It's hard.
こうか？こう！あ、こうじゃない？
Like this? Like this! Ah, isn't it like this?
オッケー、オッケー。え、これ可愛い？
Okay, okay. Wait, is this cute?
みんな正気か？可愛くないよな？
Are you guys sane? It's not cute, right?
可愛いで、ではないよな、少なくともな。ねぇ。
It's not 'cute', at least. Hey.
え、あと何がいい？何何？
Eh, what else should I do? What, what?
ブリッジ？
A bridge?
あー、いいよ、やろうか、じゃあ。いいよ。
Ah, fine, let's do it then. Sure.
みんながそんなにあーだこーだ言うんだったら、やってやりますよと。
If everyone's going to go on about it, I'll do it.
見ててね。行くよ！
Watch me. Here I go!
イェーイ、ブリッチブリッチって感じだよね
Yay, it feels like bridge-bridge, doesn't it?
よかった。いこっか。あとはあとは…
Great. Let's go. And then, and then...
え、上がってない？みんな大丈夫？
Wait, isn't it going up? Is everyone okay?
あ、ちょっとカメラさんしっかりしてもらえるかな、ねえねえねえ
Ah, wait, cameraman, can you do your job properly? Hey, hey, hey!
どう考えてもさ、出来てたよね今の
No matter how you look at it, I did it just now, right?
取り方悪いんじゃない？
Maybe the angle was bad?
ごめん、おこらないで。やーだ
Sorry, don't get mad. No way~
じゃあちょっと、マリン先輩のポーズしよっか。いくよ？
Then, shall I do Marine-senpai's pose? Here I go!
あはーん
A-haan~
え、どう？セクシー？どうどうどう？
Well, how is it? Sexy? How is it, how is it?
どうですか？
How about it?
これ、これでいいのか、本当に
Is this, is this really okay?
体育座り、あー、ペタン座り。いいよ。体育座りはさっきやったっけ？
Sitting with knees up, ah, sitting flat. Sure. Did I do the knees-up pose earlier?
どう？どうですか？
How is it? How about this?
ん？次、この次ぐらいにラストにしよっか。いい？
Hmm? Next, let's make the one after this the last one. Okay?
じゃあ、最後の何にしよっかな？何にしよっかな？
Then, what should the last one be? What should it be?
よいしょ。ん？あとは…
Heave-ho. Hmm? What else...
飼育員さんたちって、比較坂又に優しいって噂聞いたんだけど、みんな大丈夫かな？
I heard a rumor that the interns are relatively kind to Sakamata, but is everyone okay?
だっちゅーのポーズ。だっちゅーのポーズって誰？こういうやつ？いくよ？
The "Dac-chu" pose. Who does the "Dac-chu" pose? Something like this? Here I go!
だっちゅーの！
Dac-chu-no!
どう？どう？
How is it? How is it?
OK、よかったー！やったーよかったー！
OK, that's good! Yay, I'm glad!
あ！めっちゃ！
Ah! So many!
やばー！めっちゃもらった！見て！すごい！
No way! I got so many! Look! Amazing!
めちゃくちゃいっぱいもらった。これ、これいっぱい欲しかったこれ
I got a crazy amount. This, I really wanted a lot of this.
そうそうこれ。しまっときまーす。大事な奥の方にしまっときまーす
Yes, yes, this. I'll put it away. I'll store it deep inside.
よし！よかったよかった
Right! Good, good.
じゃ、沙花叉クロヱの、こんなに可愛かった沙花叉クロヱちゃんのボーナスステージもおしまいですが
Well, Sakamata Chloe's—that's the end of Chloe-chan's super cute bonus stage, but...
実は、ステージ、ここだけじゃないんです
Actually, this isn't the only stage.
おお、みんな、どんなステージだと思う？どんなだと思う？予想してみて。みんなのコメント見るわ
Oh, what kind of stage do you think it is? What kind? Try to guess. I'll check everyone's comments.
みんなの反応かわいいな。うん。おお、あ、でもみんなの予想、いい感じだよ。かなりいい感じ。近いよだいぶ
Everyone's reactions are so cute. Yeah. Oh, but everyone's guesses are pretty good. Really good. It's quite close.
風呂？ねえ、誰が3Dでお風呂入るんだよって。普段から入らないのに、お風呂入るわけないだろ3Dで
A bath? Hey, who's going to take a bath in 3D? I don't even take them normally, so there's no way I'd do it in 3D!
じゃ、次のステージに移りたいと思いまーす。移動、レッツゴー！
Now, I'd like to move on to the next stage. Moving, let's go!
呼びに行きます、お呼びに行きます
I'll go call them, I'll go call them.
お魚だー、なんか食べよっかな、どれ食べよっかな
It's a fish~ I wonder what I should eat, which one should I eat~
助けて！助けて！あー！これじゃあ無理！嫌だー助けて！
Help! Help! Ah! This is impossible! No! Help!
仲間、仲間、フレンド、フレンドだよ。わかる？フレンズ！
We're comrades, comrades! Friends, we're friends! You get it? Friends!
OK？フレンズ！
OK? Friends!
あー助けて！助けて！誰か！誰か助けて！ううー！
Ah! Help! Help! Somebody! Somebody help me! *Whimper*
じゃーん！ここどこでしょうかみんな！
Tada! Where are we, everyone?
さっき当ててくれてる子もいたんですけど、じゃーん！なんとカジノでーす！
Some of you guessed it earlier, but tada! It's actually a casino!
やったー！カジノ通ったんだよ。凄くない？いやマジで運営さんたち本当にありがとうございました
Yay! I got the casino approved! Isn't that amazing? No, seriously, staff, thank you so much.
ロマンをたくさんありがとうございましたといった感じで
Thank you so much for all the romance, so to speak.
で、あのね、ここめちゃくちゃ色々ねロマンが溢れた設備が…
And you know, this place has so many features overflowing with romance...
あるんですよ！
They have them!
見てほしいな。
I want you to see them.
くるって！
Twirl!
めためた？
Metameta?
おっ、見て！このカジノにありがちな…
Oh, look! That typical casino thing...
LED変えてないのかっていう電飾で、パチパチしてるやつ！
...where the LEDs haven't been changed and the lights are flickering!
え、めっちゃいいよねこれ、雰囲気がめちゃくちゃ出てて。
Man, this is great. It really sets the atmosphere.
そして、わぁー見て！
And, wow, look!
すごい、ルーレットもある！
Amazing, there's even a roulette table!
うわぁ、打ちてぇ。
Whoa, I want to play.
いいね、このカジノね。
This casino is nice, isn't it?
そして、はっ、はっ、はっ、はっ、来ましたよ！
And... ha, ha, ha, ha... here it is!
来ました、皆がお待ちかねの…
It's here, the one you've all been waiting for...
スロットー！イェーイ！
Slots! Yay!
いやー、いいよね、スロット打ちてぇ。
Man, slots are great. I wanna play 'em.
後で打とうかな。
Maybe I'll play later.
はい、そしてこのクソデカソファね。
Okay, and look at this humongous sofa.
何人掛けに何しゅんねんっていうクソデカソファね。
A humongous sofa that seats... who knows how many people.
これ何しゅんねん本当にね。
What's it even for, seriously?
はい、そして、わぁー！
Okay, and, wow!
ホロックスのロゴ！
The holoX logo!
これもしかして、ホロックスが経営してたりするのかな？
Wait, could it be that holoX is running this place?
どうだろうね。
I wonder.
いやー、でもめちゃくちゃかっこいいね。
Man, but it's really cool.
カジノと雰囲気も合ってて、いいなって思うよね。
It matches the casino vibe perfectly, don't you think?
そして、まぁ色々ね、魅力的な施設はあったんですけど…
And, well, there were lots of other attractive things, but...
今回はこちらのテーブルで遊びたいと思います！
This time, I want to play at this table!
じゃーじゃー、テーブル行こうかな。
Well then, let's head to the table.
レッツ・ゴー！
Let's go!
およぎまーす。
I'm swimming.
およ、およ、ドタバタ。
Swim, swim, stomp stomp.
あーっ！あちゅい！！
Ahhh! Hot!!
きたきたきたきた！！
Here it comes, here it comes!!
じゃーん、見て！
Ta-da! Look!
これ凄くない？ちゃんとテーブルについて。
Isn't this amazing? I'm actually seated at the table.
今回はゲームにチャレンジしていきたいと思います。
I'm going to take on a game challenge this time.
そして今回チャレンジするゲームは「ハイアンドロー」です！
And the game I'm challenging today is 'High and Low'!
ハイアンドロー
High and Low
ハイアンドロー、皆知ってるかな。
Does everyone know 'High and Low'?
ハイアンドローっていうのは、一枚カードをめくって…
'High and Low' is where you flip over one card...
出された数字より大きいか、高いか、低いかで…
...and guess if the next card is higher or lower...
当てていくゲームとなっております。
...than that number.
で、対戦相手が…
And my opponent is...
マネちゃん！マネちゃんじゃ、目の前にいるのに。
Mane-chan! Wait, Mane-chan is right in front of me.
殴られそう。ちょっと待って、待って、やめて。
I'm gonna get hit. Hold on, wait, stop.
え、じゃあ、え、これって…
Uh, so, wait, in this case...
マネちゃんが勝… 沙花叉が勝ったらチップをもらえて…
If Sakamata wins, I get chips, and...
マネちゃんが勝ったら…
If Mane-chan wins...
チップ取られるの？
Do I lose my chips?
いや、絶対、絶対勝つからね！絶対勝つから！
No, I'm definitely, definitely going to win! I'll win for sure!
やだやだやだ！これしないで！これしないで！
No, no, no! Don't do that! Don't do that!
沙花叉が勝つから！
Because Sakamata is going to win!
やだやだ。じゃあ、えっと、自分のカードの数字が…
No way. Okay, so if the value of my card is...
相手のカードの数字より大きいと思ったら「ハイ」。
...higher than the opponent's card, I say 'High'.
小さいと思ったら「ロー」。
If I think it's lower, I say 'Low'.
で、カードをめくって宣言が当たった場合は勝ちで…
And when the card is flipped, if my guess is correct, I win...
外れた場合は負けの簡単なルールとなってまーす。
...and if it's wrong, I lose. Those are the simple rules.
1が一番弱い、最弱で…
1 is the weakest, the absolute bottom...
キングが最強！
...and King is the strongest!
キング、キングが最強だから、キングを手元に引けば勝ちって感じかな。
King... King is the strongest, so if I get a King, I pretty much win.
ちょっと、いやー楽しみになってきた、楽しみになってきた。
Man, I'm getting excited, I'm getting excited.
じゃあ、行きますか！
Well, shall we begin?
まぁ沙花叉の強運に勝てる人はいないよね！
Well, nobody can beat Sakamata's good luck!
行きまーす。
Here I go.
お、まずはマネちゃんがめくるらしい。
Oh, looks like Mane-chan flips first.
じゃあ、マネちゃんが親として…
Okay, with Mane-chan as the dealer...
何、何だろう、何だろう。うわ、やめて。
What, what is it? What will it be? Oh, stop it.
あ、4！！
Ah, 4!!
4かー！え、これはでもさ、
A 4, huh! Well, this is...
だいぶ分かりやすいよね！
...pretty obvious, right!
いやー、ローは出ないでしょ。ローは出ない。
Man, no way it's lower. Low isn't coming out.
ローのジェスチャーしてくるけど、ローは出ないでしょ！
You're gesturing 'Low', but there's no way it's 'Low'!
え、沙花叉は「ハイ」で行きたいと思います！
Uh, Sakamata's going with 'High'!
いや、何くるか楽しみ、絶対「ハイ」に決まってるじゃん！
Man, I'm excited to see what comes next. It's obviously going to be 'High'!
いや、どう考えてもね、4よりね、ちっちゃい数字なんて出ないから。
I mean, no matter how you think about it, a number smaller than 4 isn't going to show up.
いいすか？
Ready?
めくっちゃよ。
I'm flipping it.
行きまーす、ほい！
Here goes... hah!
やったーー！！11だ！
Yesss!! It's an 11!
勝ち勝ち、イェーイ！
I win, I win! Yay!
お金戻ってきました、お金戻ってきました。
I got my money back, I got my money back.
あれ、マネちゃん弱くね？
Wait, Mane-chan, aren't you weak?
え、これ沙花叉全勝しちゃうかな？
Uh, is Sakamata going to win every single game?
いや、最強だよね！
Man, I'm the strongest!
じゃあ、次は…
Okay, next...
沙花叉が、ちょっとミスっちゃった…
Sakamata is... Oops, I made a mistake...
じゃあ沙花叉が次は親でいきたいと思います。
Okay, Sakamata's going to be the dealer next.
2回戦目ね。行くよ！
Round 2. Here we go!
さぁ沙花叉、どんなカードか皆予想して。行くよ！
Now, everyone guess what card Sakamata has. Ready!
バン！
Bam!
7！！
7!!
あー、ちょっと、ちょっとどうだろうな…
Ah, well... I wonder about this one...
どう出てくるか悩ましいところだな…
It's a tricky spot, how will it turn out...
まりちゃんどっちにするのかな?
What will Mari-chan choose?
7だよ、7。
It's a 7, a 7.
え、7って...
Eh, 7 is...
7、8、9、10、J、Q、K...
7, 8, 9, 10, J, Q, K...
ん? どっちのかな? ねえ、焦らさないで。
Hmm? Which one will it be? Hey, don't tease me.
待って待って。あ、分かった分かった。
Wait, wait. Oh, I see, I see.
でも、でもさあ。あんま変わんないよ。
But, but you know. It doesn't change much.
どうするの?
What are you going to do?
え、どう... ローで行くの? ロー? ロー?
Eh, how... Going with Low? Low? Low?
別に期待... そんな大差ないし。うん、そうだね。
I'm not really expect... It's not much of a difference. Yeah, that's right.
ローで。はい、分かった。
With Low. Yes, I got it.
いいよ。めくったら。どうぞどうぞ。
Okay. Go ahead and flip it. Please, please.
はいさあ。はあはあ。
Here we go. Hahaha.
ええー!
Ehhh!
えー!
Eh!
やだー! 目逸らさないで! やだー!
Nooo! Don't look away! Nooo!
ねえ、ずる。ずるだよ、それ。
Hey, that's unfair. That's unfair.
やだ。坂又の勝ちじゃん。
No. It's Sakamata's win, isn't it?
次、次。次だよ。絶対当てるから。
Next, next. It's next. I'll definitely get it right.
次まりちゃんのターン。どうぞ、めくって。
Next is Mari-chan's turn. Go ahead, flip it.
ねえ、焦らさないで。焦らさないで。早く早く。
Hey, don't tease me. Don't tease me. Hurry, hurry.
あー! 8かー!
Ah! It's an 8!
いやいや、もう、これは。でも、やっぱ。
No, no, this is. But, as expected.
圧倒的に頭がいいので、坂又ちゃんは。
Sakamata-chan is overwhelmingly smart, you see.
ま、ローかな? ローだよね。ロー、ロー。絶対ローだわ。
Well, Low, maybe? It's Low, right. Low, Low. It's definitely Low.
でもね、坂又ね。運いいから絶対勝てるはずなんだよ。
But you know, Sakamata is lucky, so I'm sure to win.
マジで。あの、運で負けたことあんましないから。
Seriously. I haven't really lost because of luck.
ガチで。
For real.
じゃあ、行きますよ。
Okay, here I go.
はい!
Yes!
あー! やったー! よかったー!
Ah! I did it! I'm so glad!
今、頭バグってさ。え、1って最強だっけ? みたいになってた。
My brain just glitched out. I was like, "Wait, is 1 the strongest?"
やったー! 勝ち勝ち!
I did it! Win, win!
やったー、やったー。え、まりちゃん弱...
Yay, yay. Eh, Mari-chan is weak...
あ、見て見て。チップの量、これヤバくない?
Oh, look, look. Isn't this amount of chips crazy?
え、坂又、これ大富豪じゃん。
Eh, Sakamata is a multi-millionaire now.
このままちょっと。全勝ちしていきたいな。
I want to keep going like this and win them all.
よし。じゃあ、行きますか。
Alright. Shall we go then?
じゃあ、坂又が次親だからね。いくよ。
Then, Sakamata will be the dealer next. Here I go.
はい!
Yes!
10... 10ですよ。
10... it's a 10.
10ですよ。
It's a 10.
どうします?
What are you going to do?
ねえー! やだー!
Nooo! Nooo!
まりちゃんのターンで全然いいよ。
It's totally fine if it's Mari-chan's turn.
いやいや、10ってさ。10ってちょっと高いから。
No, no, 10 is. 10 is a bit high.
やめて、やめて、やめてよ。
Stop it, stop it, stop it.
やめて、ローじゃないでしょ。やだ、やだ。
Stop it, it's not Low, right? No, no.
ちょっと返して、やだー。
Give it back a bit, nooo.
なんで? ひどいよー。もー。やだ、やだ。
Why? You're mean. Jeez. No, no.
絶対坂又の勝ちなんだから。
I'm definitely going to win.
はあ! 坂又の勝ちじゃん。
Haa! It's Sakamata's win.
え、え、ねえ、煽ってた。
Eh, eh, hey, you were taunting me.
ねえ、煽ってた。くせに、負け負けの負けじゃん。
Hey, you were taunting me. And yet, you lost, lost, lost.
ねーねー、坂又強くない?
Hey, hey, isn't Sakamata strong?
え、これ何回目だっけ? 分かんなくなっちゃった。
Eh, how many times has it been? I've lost track.
二回目?
Second time?
見て見て、このさ、チップの山。
Look, look at this pile of chips.
絶対坂又が負けるわけないね、こっから。
There's no way Sakamata can lose from here.
よし、よし。じゃあまりちゃんどうぞ、と。
Good, good. Then Mari-chan, go ahead.
え、これ勝ちじゃん。やったー。
Eh, I win this. Yay.
え、あ、ロー、ロー、ロー。
Eh, ah, Low, Low, Low.
ねえ、やめて、ここ外さないで。
Hey, stop it, don't miss this.
ロー、ロー、ロー。はい、めくって、めくって。
Low, Low, Low. Okay, flip it, flip it.
早く、早く。
Hurry, hurry.
早く、早く。どう? どう? どう? やったー!
Hurry, hurry. How is it? How is it? How is it? Yay!
坂又ラッシュ! ねえ、なん、なん。よし、よし、よし。
Sakamata rush! Hey, what, what. Good, good, good.
イェー! 見てこのチップの山。イェー!
Yay! Look at this pile of chips. Yay!
これ、勝ちましたね。
I've won this, haven't I?
勝ちが見えます。
I can see the victory.
よしよ、坂又が親のターンですよ。
Alright, it's Sakamata's turn as the dealer.
じゃあ、めくりますね。
Well then, I'll flip it.
いいかな? んんん。
Ready? Hmmm.
ほい!
Hoi!
変えてもらえますか?
Can I have it changed?
店長、なんかズルされてます。
Manager, I'm being cheated somehow.
今。なんかやってます、この人。
Right now. This person is doing something.
ちょっとお、な、何ですか?
Hey, what is it?
あ、どっち? うえ?
Ah, which one? Up?
あ、ハイ。あ、ハイだって、みんな。
Ah, High. Oh, she said High, everyone.
ハイだって、ハイだって。じゃあハイで行きましょう、ハイで。
She said High, she said High. Then let's go with High, with High.
ハイだって。はい、はい、はい。イェー!
She said High. High, High, High. Yay!
ハイ、ハイ、ハイ。あ、聞いてます? ちょっと、お姉さん?
High, High, High. Oh, are you listening? Hey, miss?
ハイ、とおって。ハイ、とおってよ。
High, go through. High, please go through.
やった、やったー。おーん、て言いながら、ハイにする...
I did it, I did it. Saying "On", then choosing High...
あれ? ねえ、おかしいよね!
Huh? Hey, that's weird, right!
ハイ、とおったじゃん一回! 絶対おかしいよねこのゲーム!
High went through once! This game is definitely weird!
え？ちょっと待って、これ絶対…
Eh? Wait a second, this is definitely...
え？ちょっと待って。え、冷静になろう、大丈夫大丈夫。
Eh? Wait. Let's stay calm, it's okay, it's okay.
やだ！ずるいよ！ずるい！ねえ、坂又の…
No! That's cheating! Cheating! Hey, Sakamata's...
坂又のチップ減った。悲しい。
Sakamata's chips decreased. So sad.
ねえ…ラ…ラスト？ラスト？
Hey... last? Last?
え…ちょっと…え、シンクロニズムどっち？
Eh... wait... which one is "synchronism"?
ちょっと、坂又に味方して？
Wait, take Sakamata's side?
え？勝ったら1000万枚だった。え、
Eh? If I won, it was 10 million chips. Eh,
スロットの万枚台2000台？あはははは！
2,000 slot machines with 10,000 chips each? Hahaha!
やったー！これ絶対勝つよみんな、協力して協力して。
Yay! We're definitely gonna win this, everyone, help me out.
みんな、一緒に勝つよ、わかった？みんな、一緒に勝つよ。
Everyone, let's win together, okay? Everyone, let's win together.
ちょっと応援してね、どっちがいいか考えてね。
Cheer for me, think about which one is better.
じゃあ、マリンちゃんのターンどうぞ。
Now, Marine-chan's turn, please.
ラストだよ、ねえマジで。
It's the last one, seriously.
え、大丈夫だよね？大丈夫だよね？
Eh, it'll be okay, right? It'll be okay, right?
はい！はぁー！みんな！
Yes! Haa! Everyone!
え、みんなこれさ、圧倒的ローだよね？
Eh, everyone, this is an overwhelming "low", right?
え、圧倒的ローですよ！みんな、みんなどっちにする？
Eh, it's an overwhelming "low"! Everyone, which one will you choose?
どっちにするこれ？え、ローだよね？
Which one for this? Eh, it's "low", right?
え、もうみんなに聞くまでもないかこれ。どうどうどう？
Eh, I guess I don't even need to ask. How is it?
みんなどっちがいい？ローだよね？
Everyone, which one do you want? It's "low", right?
あ、ローだよね？そうだよね？
Ah, it's "low", right? That's right?
あーよかったよかったよかった。みんなと意見一致してた。よかった。
Ah, good, good, good. My opinion matched everyone's. Good.
え、何？なんか全額賭け…え、なんかすごい今ファイナルアンサー？
Eh, what? Like, bet the whole amount? Eh, like "final answer" now?
全額賭けますか？って言われて、え…
Being asked "Will you bet the whole amount?", eh...
いやいやいや、全ベで。全ベでローで行きたいと思います。
No no no, all bet. I'll go with all bet on "low".
や、でもね、これで負けること絶対ないと思う。
But you know, there's no way I'll lose this.
え、行けるからね、まじで。え、待って、本当緊張してきた。
Eh, I can do it, seriously. Eh, wait, I'm getting really nervous.
行けますよね？バイゾ。はい！
I can do it, right? Baizo. Yes!
…あああ！やだー！あああああ！やだやだ！
...Aaah! Nooo! Aaaaa! No, no!
ねえやだ！どうしてなの？やめてやめて！
Hey, no! Why? Stop it, stop it!
やめて！え、え、坂又のチップ…
Stop! Eh, eh, Sakamata's chips...
あああ行かないで！行かないで！行かないで！
Aaah, don't go! Don't go! Don't go!
やだやだやだ！ここ、ここ痛い！
No no no! Here, it hurts here!
ここ、ここならまだ生きてるこの中！
Here, it's still alive in here!
この中、ねえ痛い！どうしてなの？
In here, hey, it hurts! Why?
やだやだやだ！俺、これ…あはははは！
No no no! Me, this... hahaha!
坂又のチップもらえなかった…ねえひどい！
I couldn't get Sakamata's chips... Hey, so cruel!
ぴえぴえぴえぴえ、マリンちゃんに…ひどい！
Pien pien pien pien, to Marine-chan... so cruel!
坂又勝ってたのに！何このゲーム！
Even though Sakamata was winning! What is this game!
もう水…いっぱい…え、なんで水渡されたの？
Already, water... so much... eh, why was I given water?
黙れって？ねえひどい！ひどいよ！
To shut up? Hey, so cruel! That's cruel!
え、これで終わり？可哀想なんだが坂又。
Eh, is this the end? Sakamata is so pitiful.
はぁー…2000枚？2000万枚？
Haa... 2,000 chips? 20 million chips?
はぁー…何枚くれるの？何枚くれるんだ？
Haa... how many will you give me? How many will you give?
え？これ…これがご褒美？
Eh? This... this is the reward?
きちゃめら…きちゃ…ちょっと…
Kichamera... kicha... wait...
きちゃめら…これがご褒美なの？
Kichamera... is this the reward?
ふざけるか！ふざけるか、あっち行け！
Are you kidding me! Are you kidding, go away!
やだ！坂又の勝ちを！お前のせいで！
No! Sakamata's win! Because of you!
うわあああああ！お前がいたから負けたんじゃないの？
Uwaaaaa! Is it because you were here that I lost?
ひどいよ！あんまりだ！ううう…
So cruel! Too much! Uuu...
ううう…なんで負けたの坂又。
Uuu... why did Sakamata lose.
ひどい。ひどいよ、あんまりだ。
So cruel. So cruel, too much.
誰か助けて。誰か…誰か…
Someone help me. Someone... someone...
え、これだけなんですか？
Eh, is this all?
え、他に本当に何もないの？
Eh, is there really nothing else?
あ…分かりました。じゃあ…はい。
Ah... I understand. Then... yes.
こいつ、こいついるまんまなんだね。OK。はい。
This guy, he's just gonna stay here. OK. Yes.
はい、じゃあちょっと負け負けに負けちゃいましたが、
Yes, well, I lost and lost big time, but...
坂又のかっこいいところをね、見てほしいなと思うので、
I want you to see Sakamata's cool side.
ここでちょっと気づいた人もいるんじゃないかな？
Maybe some people have noticed?
なんとライブステージがこの部屋にはあるんですね。
There's actually a live stage in this room.
そこで坂又、歌わせていただきたいと思います。
So I, Sakamata, would like to sing there.
どうどう？いいかな？いいかな？どう？
How about it? Is it okay? Is it okay? How?
こいつしかいないんで。ね、いいよ。
Since there's only this guy. Right, it's okay.
いや、お前のレスポンスは全然求めてない。はい。
No, I'm not looking for your response at all. Yes.
では行きたいと思います！レッツ・ゴー！
Now, here I go! Let's go!
はい、ここでお知らせです！6月16日木曜日20時から、
Yes, here's an announcement! On Thursday, June 16th at 8:00 PM,
博衣こよりの3Dがお披露目されます！
Hakui Koyori's 3D debut will be held!
こんこよー！こんこよー、博衣こよりだよー！
Konkoyo! Konkoyo, it's Hakui Koyori!
あはは、ちょっと馬鹿にしすぎ。おへそがね、
Hahaha, I'm making fun of her too much. Her belly button,
めちゃくちゃエッチなのとお、
is super sexy, and...
あと実は今隠れているんですけど、足もね、素晴らしくエッチでした。
Actually, it's hidden now, but her legs were also wonderfully sexy.
そしてしっぽもね、みんなお待ちかね、お待たせしましたのしっぽもみんな…
And her tail too, everyone's been waiting, sorry to keep you waiting, her tail also...
...ということで、3D配信楽しみに待っててください！
...so please look forward to the 3D stream!
はい、沙花叉からのニュースはこちら、ドドン！
Alright, here's the news from Sakamata, ta-da!
沙花叉クロヱの...なんだっけ？誕生日記念グッズ...き、へぇ...噛んじゃった。
Sakamata Chloe's... what was it? Birthday commemorative goods... ki, eh... I stumbled over my words.
はい、アクリルジオラマスタンド、販売中です！
Yes, the acrylic diorama stand is on sale!
見て見て、これ真似してみるわ。どう？似てる？どう？
Look, look, I'll try to mimic it. How is it? Do I look like it? How about it?
こんな可愛いアクリルジオラマスタンドがついております。
This cute acrylic diorama stand is included.
そして、噂になっちゃってるとか、なってないとか、なってないとか聞きますけど...
And, I hear it's becoming a rumor, or not, or not, but...
...噂のブレスレット！
...the rumored bracelet!
そして、チョーカーチャーム、沙花叉のこれとお揃いです！
And the choker charm, it's the same as Sakamata's!
そして、記念ボイス！こちら全てがセットになっている全部セットでは...
And the commemorative voice! In the Full Set which includes all of these...
...特典ボイスと、そして直筆メッセージ付きポストカードも付きます！
...you also get a bonus voice and a postcard with a handwritten message!
特典ボイスでは沙花叉が珍しくちょっとだけデレてたり、デレてなかったり。
In the bonus voice, Sakamata might be acting a bit sweet for once, or she might not.
そして直筆メッセージ付きポストカードは、汚ねぇ字に思いを込めました。
And for the postcard with a handwritten message, I put my feelings into my messy handwriting.
マジで読めるかどうかわかんないけど、みんなには読めるかな？
I honestly don't know if you'll be able to read it, but can you guys?
ぜひ、よろしくお願いします！バイバイ！
Please check it out! Bye-bye!
バイバイバイバイバイ...
Bye-bye-bye-bye-bye...
One, two, one...
Deal with the devil
作詞・作曲：ryo(supercell)
Lyrics/Composition: ryo(supercell)
アップダウンは世の常
Ups and downs are the way of the world
クズ引いたって動じない
Even if I draw a bad hand, I won't flinch
肝心なのは Strong Mind
The important thing is a Strong Mind
出し抜いて Survive
Outsmart them and Survive
行きつく先は Heaven or hell
The final destination is Heaven or hell
この世界のルール
The rules of this world
たった一つ 勝者こそが正義
There's only one: victory is justice
女は度胸
A woman needs courage
震わせるのアイツを
Make him tremble
やれること なんだってやる
I'll do whatever it takes
あたしは賭け狂いのクイーン
I'm the queen of gambling
お見通しよ You doubt me
I see right through you, You doubt me
読み切って レッツ Showdown
Read it all, let's Showdown
震えちゃうほど 難しいって
So difficult it makes me tremble
あたしのものにする
I'll make it mine
あなたの髪の一本まで全部
Every single strand of your hair
あげないわ 誰にも
I won't give it to anyone
震えてるわよ ほら
Look, you're trembling
降ろさせはしないわ
I won't let you fold
Uhhhn 最高
Uhhhn, the best
もっと止まらないわスリル
The thrill won't stop
誰にも触らせないこの Money
I won't let anyone touch this Money
あげないわ 誰にも
I won't give it to anyone
さあ Com'on 覚悟キメて
Now, come on, steel yourself
震えちゃぶれないハート
A heart that doesn't waver even when trembling
欲しがるようじゃね まだベイビー
If you're still wanting it, you're still a baby
誰にも あげない
I won't give it to anyone
感じさせてあげるわ
I'll make you feel it
あなた内緒だわ
It's a secret with you
ほら見せてあげる
Look, I'll show you
秘密って甘いの
Secrets are sweet
仕掛けて 罠にはめるわ
Setting it up and trapping you
油断誘うのよ
I'll tempt your carelessness
思考を止めたら ジ・エンド
If you stop thinking, it's the end
何も知らないような表情で
With a look like you know nothing
落とすわあなたを
I'll bring you down
お見通しよ You doubt me
I see right through you, You doubt me
読み切って レッツ Showdown
Read it all, let's Showdown
見逃さない どんな小さなズルだって
I won't miss even the smallest cheat
あたしの目はごまかされないわ
My eyes won't be deceived
あげないわ 誰にも
I won't give it to anyone
勝った相手は骨まで
My defeated opponent, down to the bone
愛し尽くしてあげる
I'll love you completely
狙った獲物は逃がさない
I won't let the targeted prey escape
唇濡らして いただくわ
Wetting my lips, I'll have you
Babe
ダイヤのジャックで手が揃う
Hand's complete with the Jack of Diamonds
笑みを殺し 待つだけ
Kill the smile and just wait
あたしのポーカーフェイスは It's perfect
My poker face is, It's perfect
一分の隙も見せたりしないわ
I won't show even a moment's weakness
恍惚感じてるわ
I'm feeling ecstatic
お望みは最後まで
To the very end of your wishes
見てばっかりいないで
Don't just keep on watching
あたしとしていない？
Won't you do it with me?
読み切って　レイズ　Showdown
Read it all, Raise, Showdown
迷い抜けて　Oh, It's showtime
Escape the hesitation, Oh, It's showtime
全部全部見透かして
See through everything, everything
あたしのものにする　あなたの髪の一本まで全部
I'll make it all mine, down to every single strand of your hair
A million dollars　賭けてるわ　坊や
I'm betting a million dollars, boy
とことんまで行くわ
I'll go all the way
全部全部たまらないわ
Everything, everything is irresistible
誰にも触らせない　このMoney
I won't let anyone touch this Money
A million dollars　さあ　カモン　覚悟決めて
A million dollars, now come on, make up your mind
灰になるまで打って
Shoot until you're nothing but ash
欲しがるようじゃね　まだベイビー
If you're still wanting more, you're still a baby
誰にも負けない　完遂させて　Aww...
I won't lose to anyone, let me see it through, Aww...
誰にも負けない　完遂させて
I won't lose to anyone, let me see it through
ふぅー！
Whew!
はぁ、はい、みんな！どうだったー！？
Haa, okay, everyone! How was it!?
結構、頑張ってみたんだけど、どうどうどうどう？
I worked pretty hard on it, so how was it, how was it, how was it, how was it?
いや、かなりね、練習もたくさん頑張って、
No, really, I practiced a lot,
練習も！本当ーにたくさん頑張って！来たので、
Practice too! I really, really worked hard to get here,
上手くいけてたらいいなって思います。どう、良かった？
So I hope it went well. How was it, was it good?
あ、良かった？あー良かったー！マジで良かったー！
Oh, it was good? Ah, thank goodness! I'm so glad!
イエーイ！
Yay!
可愛かった？
Was I cute?
素晴らしい？ありがとうございます！
Splendid? Thank you very much!
イエーイ！
Yay!
ではでは、ライブはまだまだ続きます！
Well then, the live is still going on!
今度は水族館で準備ができてるみたいだから、
It seems like the aquarium is ready now,
移動しちゃうよー！
So let's head over there!
いいかなー？
Are you ready?
いくよー？
Here we go!
レッツ！ゴー！すいすいすいー！
Let's! Go! Suisuisui!
ふぅー。
Whew.
やっぱ水だよな。
Water is the best, after all.
やっぱシャチ...
After all, for an orca...
うわぁ！
Whoa!
びっくりした！ねぇ！
That scared me! Hey!
ねぇ、誰これ打ったの？
Hey, who threw this?
いらない！
I don't want it!
もう帰れって！ガタガタガタ...
Go home already! *shaking*
ふぅ。
Phew.
おわいっ！うわぁー！
Whoa! Waaah!
帰って！沙花叉の出番！マジで！
Go away! It's Sakamata's turn! Seriously!
うわぁー！やっべ！
Waaah! No way!
帰れー！お前！いらない！
Go home! You! I don't want you here!
おらおらおら！
Take this, this, this!
くっそ、お前...はぁ、くっそ...
Damn you... haa, damn it...
はーい、到着しました！水族館！
Okay, we've arrived! The aquarium!
実はね、さっき言ってなかったんだけど、すごい仕掛けを用意してもらったんです！
Actually, I didn't say earlier, but they've prepared a great gimmick for me!
じゃーん！天井、ドカーン！
Ta-da! The ceiling, kaboom!
うわぁー！すごーい！天井が閉じました！みんな、これで課金も怖くないねって...
Whoa! Amazing! The ceiling has closed! Everyone, now we don't have to fear microtransactions anymore... wait...
全然関係ない...。てか天井じゃないんですけど、はい！
That's completely unrelated... and it's not even the ceiling, but anyway!
めっちゃいいでしょ？沙花叉の仮面の模様になってるんですよー！めちゃくちゃいいよね！
Isn't it great? It's in the pattern of Sakamata's mask! It's so cool, right?
そして、まだあるんですね。いくよー？
And there's more. Here we go!
せーの、だーん！
One, two, bang!
すんごーい！
Incre-dible!
すごーい！見て見て！
Amazing! Look, look!
水族館の中に、みんな入り込んじゃった！めちゃくちゃいいよね！
Everyone has entered inside the aquarium! It's so cool, right?
このセットにもめちゃくちゃ合う曲を選んできました！
I've chosen a song that fits this set perfectly!
みんな、聴いてくれるかな？
Will everyone listen to it?
すごい？あ、良かった良かった！
It's amazing? Oh, good, I'm glad!
じゃあ、みんな聴いてほしいな。いくよ？
Well then, I want everyone to hear it. Here we go.
歌います。「海の幽霊」。
I'm going to sing. "Umi no Yuurei" (Spirits of the Sea).
明け放たれたこの部屋には　誰もいない
In this room thrown wide open, there is no one
海の幽霊
作詞・作曲　米津玄師
Umi no Yuurei (Spirits of the Sea)
Lyrics and composition by Kenshi Yonezu
潮風の匂い　染み付いた
The scent of the sea breeze has soaked in
椅子が一つ
There is one chair
あなたが迷わないように
So that you won't get lost
開けておくよ
I'll leave it open
軋む戸を叩いて
Knock on the creaking door
何から話せばいいのか
Where should I start?
分からなくなる
I don't know anymore
かな
Maybe...
星が降る夜にあなたに会えた
I met you on a night when stars were falling
あの夜を忘れはしない
I will never forget that night
大切なことは言葉にならない
Important things cannot be put into words
夏の日に起きたすべて
Everything that happened on that summer day
思いがけず光るのは海の幽霊
What glows unexpectedly are the spirits of the sea
茹だる夏の夕に梢が
In the sweltering summer evening, the treetops...
船を見送る
...see the ship off
いくつかの歌を囁く
Whispering several songs
花を散らして
Scattering flowers
あなたがどこかで笑う声が聞こえる
I hear your voice laughing somewhere
熱い頬の手触り
The feel of hot cheeks
捩れた道を進んだらそのまぶたが
If I go down the twisted path, those eyelids...
開く
...open
離れ離れでもときめくもの
Things that make the heart flutter even when apart
叫べ今は幸せと
Shout that you're happy now
大切なことは言葉にならない
Important things cannot be put into words
跳ねる光に溶かして
Dissolve in the bouncing light
星が降る夜にあなたに会えた
I met you on a night when stars were falling
あの時を忘れはしない
I will never forget that time
大切なことは言葉にならない
Important things cannot be put into words
夏の日に起きたすべて
Everything that happened on that summer day
思いがけず光るのは海の幽霊
What glows unexpectedly are the spirits of the sea
風薫る砂浜で
On the wind-scented beach
また会いましょう
Let's meet again
あー！ あー！ うわ、めちゃくちゃ緊張しちゃった。
Ah! Ah! Wow, I was so nervous.
ちょっと声震えちゃってたら、ごめんなさい。
Sorry if my voice was shaking a bit.
でも、めっちゃ練習したの。どうだった？どうだった？
But I practiced a lot. How was it? How was it?
いい感じだったね？ね？ね？ね？
It was pretty good, right? Right?
よかった。
Good.
沙花叉がね、海の生物なので、「海の幽霊」、ちょっと選んでみました。
Since Sakamata is a sea creature, I chose "Spirits of the Sea."
めちゃくちゃね、このステージも、綺麗なステージなので、合ってたんじゃないかなって思います。
And since this stage is also such a beautiful stage, I thought it suited it well.
どうだった？どうだった？あ、よかった。あ、よかった。
How was it? How was it? Ah, good. Ah, good.
ではでは、まだまだね、3Dの姿、お見せしたかったんですが、
Well then, I still wanted to show you more of my 3D form, but...
次が最後の曲になります。
The next one will be the last song.
実はね、配信後に、今は秘密だよってなってたんだけど、
Actually, it was supposed to be a secret for now, but after the stream...
「キメラ」の歌ってみたがプレミア公開で上がりますので、
my "Chimera" cover will be released as a premiere,
そちらの方も楽しみに待っててください。9時半から上がります。
so please look forward to that as well. It'll be up starting from 9:30.
よろしくお願いします。
Thank you.
じゃあ、次の曲、ラストですが、いきたいと思います。
Well then, it's the last song, but let's go.
それでは聴いてください。「あなたが居ることで」。
Please listen to it. "Because You Are Here".
あなたがいることで
歌：沙花叉クロヱ
作詞・作曲：Uru
Anata ga Iru Koto de
Vocal: Sakamata Chloe
Lyrics/Composition: Uru
どんな言葉で
With what words
今あなたに伝えられるだろう
could I convey it to you now?
不器用な僕だけど
I'm clumsy, but
ちゃんとあなたに届くように
I hope this properly reaches you.
明日が見えなくなって
When I can't see tomorrow,
信じることが怖くなって
and I become afraid of believing,
過去を悔やんでは責めたりもしたけれど
I regretted the past and even blamed myself, but...
僕を愛し続けて
The person who continued
くれた人
to love me.
もしも世界が終わっても
Even if the world ends,
会えない日々が続いたとしても
even if the days we can't meet continue,
僕はずっとあなたを想うよ
I will always be thinking of you.
あの日僕にくれたあなたの笑顔が
The smile you gave me that day
生きる力と勇気をくれたんだ
gave me the strength and courage to live.
星が見えない孤独な夜でも
Even on lonely nights when no stars can be seen,
あなたがいる　ただそれだけで強くなれる
you are there, and just for that, I can become strong.
目が合えば笑って
When our eyes meet, you smile,
一緒にいれば楽しくて
being together is fun.
共に過ごした毎日は
The days we spent together
かけがえのないものだった
were irreplaceable.
向かい風が冷たくて
The headwind is cold,
忘れてしまいそうになるけど
and I almost forget, but...
通り過ぎてきた何気ない日々の中に
Within the casual days that have passed,
僕らの幸せは確かにあった
our happiness was certainly there.
もしも負けそうな夜の中で
If in a night when I feel like giving in,
一人静かに泣いているのなら
you are crying alone in silence,
あなたが僕を信じてくれたように
just as you believed in me,
次は僕がその手を強く握るから
next time, I will grip that hand of yours tightly.
傷つくことから逃げていた
I was running away from being hurt.
この心動かすのは
What moves this heart
弱さを見せないあなたが見せてくれた
is what you, who doesn't show weakness, showed me...
初めて見せた涙
the tears you showed for the first time.
いつか僕に話してくれた
One day you told me,
あなたが描いた未来の中に
within the future you envisioned,
僕ら一緒にいられるように
so that we can be together.
あなたがいることで
By you being there,
どんな明日も歩いていける光になるから
you become the light that allows me to walk into any tomorrow.
星が見えない孤独な夜でも
Even on lonely nights when no stars can be seen,
信じられる　僕らならここで笑える日を
I can believe, that for us, the day we can smile here will come.
飼育員さんへ
沙花叉クロヱを見つけてくれて応援してくれてありがとう！
To the Keepers,
thank you for finding Sakamata Chloe and supporting me!
みんなの声が沙花叉の宝物だよ。
これからも沢山の思い出をつくっていこうね！大好きだよ
Everyone's voices are Sakamata's treasure.
Let's keep making many memories! I love you all!
はぁ... すみません。引っ張りすぎて...
ちょっとごめんなさい。
Haa... I'm sorry. I dragged it out too much...
I'm a bit sorry.
はい！ということで、今日の3Dお披露目ライブ、
みんな来てくれてありがとうございました。
All right! And so, thank you everyone
for coming to today's 3D debut live.
たくさん頑張ったし、みんながね、こうやって応援してくれて、
沙花叉も3D化できたと思いますので、
I worked hard, and because of everyone's support,
I think I was able to get a 3D model,
これからもね、ライブや色んな目標に向かって
頑張っていきたいと思います。
so I want to keep working hard towards
lives and various other goals from now on.
本当にみんな、いつも応援ありがとうございます！
ありがとうございました！
Really, everyone, thank you for always
supporting me! Thank you very much!
今日は来てくれてありがとうみんな。
本当にありがとうね。
Thank you for coming today, everyone.
Really, thank you.
じゃあね！ありがとう！
See ya! Thank you!
おい！ ちょちょちょちょ！ ちょちょ！
Hey! Wait wait wait wait! Wait wait!
うわあ可愛い沙花叉ちゃんいいけど、
あの、えーーー！！
Wow, cute Sakamata-chan is fine but,
uh, WHAAAT?!